{
    "subject": "Saeed_Akhtar_Mirza",
    "predicate": "directed",
    "object": "Mohan_Joshi_Hazir_Ho!",
    "human_readable": "Saeed Akhtar Mirza directed the film Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.943630039691925,
            "question": "Name a film directed by Saeed Akhtar Mirza."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9017500877380371,
            "question": "What is the name of the film directed by Saeed Akhtar Mirza?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8526813387870789,
            "question": "Who directed the film Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7302736639976501,
            "question": "What year was the film Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho! released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.678667426109314,
            "question": "Where was the film Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho! filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6082810163497925,
            "question": "What is the plot of Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5317420959472656,
            "question": "Why is the film Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho! considered significant?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.512164294719696,
            "question": "What genre is the film Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4780336022377014,
            "question": "Who are some of the actors in Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.44637227058410645,
            "question": "Is Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho! a fictional story?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Saeed Akhtar Mirza directed the film Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!",
            "html": "yago_14541_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of the actors in Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!",
            "html": "yago_14541_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre is the film Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!",
            "html": "yago_14541_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Why is the film Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho! considered significant?",
            "html": "yago_14541_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14541_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14541_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14541_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14541_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14541_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14541_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14541_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14541_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14541_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_14541_79.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that confirms Saeed Akhtar Mirza directed the film \"Mohan Joshi Hazir Ho!\". This is directly stated in multiple documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}